Patrik Potocny

Front-End Developer

patrikp.dev

in linkedin.com/in/patrikpotocny

github.com/patrick-potocny

patrik@patrikp.dev

6

+421 940 116 860

Summary

When the COVID-19 pandemic began, I saw an opportunity to learn something new. With a lifelong interest in technology, I dove deep into the world of programming and haven't stopped learning and creating awesome projects since. After 3 years, I have gained proficiency in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, TypeScript, and SCSS, and have utilized these technologies to design visually pleasing and user-friendly websites and web applications.

My most recent project is a full-stack web application(joblyapp.net) that manages and organizes all aspects of the job search, making life easier for job seekers. It is built with React, TypeScript, SCSS, Firebase, and follows best coding practices. Passionate about creating things that provide value and solve real-world problems, I am always seeking new challenges and opportunities to learn.

Experience

Jobly (joblyapp.net)

iii January 2023 - March 2023

EEE December 2022 - January 2023

iii December 2022 - January 2023

Designer & Front-End Developer

HTML | SCSS | TypeScript | React | Next.js | Firebase

- Jobly is a web application to manage and organize all aspects of job search, including job postings, interviews, and notes, making life easier for job seekers.
- Designed the whole application with a focus on user experience.
- I utilized HTML/SCSS, TypeScript, React and Next.js to develop the front-end of the web application, ensuring that it was optimized for performance and responsiveness.

Case Study

Code

BeBetter(bebetter.chat)

Designer & Front-End Developer HTML | SCSS | JavaScript | React

- BeBetter is an Al-powered chatbot that uses the most advanced NLP model available. That
 enables it to understand and respond to users' needs and give personalized advice on any
 tonic.
- Designed the whole application with a focus on user experience.
- Developing the front-end, I utilized HTML/SCSS, JavaScript, and React to ensure that the final product was visually appealing and user-friendly.

Case Study

Code

AssetNet(assetnet.co)

Designer & Front-End Developer HTML | SCSS | JavaScript | React

- AssetNet is a web application that presents the latest data on users' selected assets in a customizable and easily accessible interface
- Designed the whole application with a focus on user experience.
- In creation of the front-end, I employed HTML/SCSS, JavaScript, and React, making the web application pixel-perfect.

Case Study

Code

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Unit Testing
- SCSS
- Git
- JavaScript
- UI/UX
- TypeScript
- Figma
- React
- Next.js

Education

Google UX Design (Certificate)

February 2022 - April 2022

Stredná priemyselná škola technická, Trnava

2018 - 2022